bitstarz.com 2019-06-07

# Privacy Policy - BitStarz Casino

  * ### GENERAL

    1. This Privacy Policy explains what personal data we collect from players, for what reason we collect it and how we utilise it. Before using our website, please read this Privacy Policy carefully 

The website BitStarz is operated by Direx Limited, Stasinou 1, MITSI Building 1, 1st Floor, Flat/Office 4, Plateia Eleftherias, Nicosia, Cyprus (“Company”) and all game content is licensed through the Direx NV, Heelsumstraat 51 E-Commerce Park, Curacao. Registration number 131879., a company registered by the Government of Curaçao, as an Information Provider legally authorized to conduct online egaming operations from Curaçao. Egaming Licensing and Supervision is provided by Antillephone N.V. 

Please note that this Privacy Policy constitutes an agreement between you and the Casino. We may periodically make modifications to this Policy. While we will do our best to notify you of such changes, we recommend that you revisit this Privacy Policy regularly. 

### INFORMATION COLLECTED

    1. The Personal Information which we may request to use and process shall include, without limitation: 

a) Any of the information that you provide to us when filling in the forms on our account registration pages, as well as any other data that you submit to us via the Website or email (e.g. first and last name, date of birth, physical address, email address, phone number); 

b) Correspondence made via the Website, email, telephone and web chat or through other means of communication; 

c) Survey participations or any other customer assessments that we may carry out from time to time; 

d) All customer account transaction history, whether this takes place through the Website(s) or via other means of communication; 

e) Website logins and their details, including traffic data, GeoIP location data, weblogs, activity logs and other traffic information recorded on the system. 

### USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

    1. We will use the Personal Information we collect from you to be able to deliver our Services and for the following purposes:

a) Processing your bets and transactions. This includes your use of credit card and online payment systems;

b) Providing you with customer support service, including assistance with setting up, operating and managing your account; 

c) Complying with legal and regulatory responsibilities;

d) Creating personal profiles for our customers, which may lead to Loyalty Points and Rewards;

e) Undertaking necessary measures for Member Account security and to identify the required verification checks; 

f) Analysing customer trends through market study assessments (participation in surveys, if any are sent to you, is not obligatory and you always have a choice as to whether you would like to partake); 

g) Providing our registered players with information about our promotional offers, products and services, or providing promotional information from our selected business partners, associates and affiliates, where players would have specifically consented to receiving marketing material; 

h) Monitoring and investigating transactions for the purposes of preventing fraud, money laundering and other irregular gaming activities 

### MARKETING COMMUNICATION

    1. Unless you have elected not to receive promotional information, we may also use your Personal Information, including your email address and phone number, to provide you with marketing communications regarding products, services and promotions. This may also include information about other gaming products and services from our business partners (such as game providers), which would have been carefully selected by us. Should you prefer to stop receiving marketing and other advertising material, you may opt out of this service by administrating your account settings or by contacting our customer support service on [support@bitstarz.com](mailto:support@bitstarz.com). 

You are also to note that by accepting any contest prize or winnings from us, you consent to the use of your name and likeness for advertising and promotional purposes without additional compensation, except where prohibited by law. 

### OBTAINING PERSONAL INFORMATION

    1. We shall not collect any Personal Information about you without your knowledge. We may however automatically collect certain data and receive personal information about you where you would have provided such information through the use of our services and through your interactions with us. 

We may also receive certain Personal Information from online vendors and service providers, as well as from customer lists lawfully acquired from third-party vendors. In addition, we retain the right to engage the services of third-party service providers to provide technical support, so as to process your online transactions and to maintain your Member Account. 

Please understand that we may be granted access to any information you may provide to such vendors, service providers and third-party e-commerce services. Rest assured that we will use and safeguard any Personal Information so obtained, as set out in this Policy. Any information that you provide will only be disclosed to third parties outside the Company in accordance with this Privacy Policy and we shall take necessary steps to ensure that our agreements with third-party service providers and online vendors always protect your private information. 

### SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

    1. We may pass information that you have given us to other entities within our group of companies and to our business partners. These companies may include our parent companies, their parent companies and all of the subsidiaries of these respective companies, as well as other companies with whom we carry out business and hold necessary agreements. Data processing of your information may be undertaken by Direx N.V. or by another company in the group of companies, which may use a third party to fulfill such data processing needs. 

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves transmission of data. We may therefore also disclose information that you have given us to our business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract obligations we may have entered into with them or you. Details of any third party to whom your financial information may be passed on to for the fulfillment of your use of our services, shall be made available to you. 

You should also note that in order to provide you with an efficient service, we and/or our service providers might require transferring your personal data from one country to another in the European Union (EU) and European Free Trade Association (EFTA) regions and also to some data processors that may be based outside of the European Economic Area (EEA). Therefore, by browsing the Website and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our (or our suppliers or sub-contractors) processing of your personal data in these countries. We shall always take all reasonable steps to ensure that your information and data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

Nevertheless, your Personal Information will always be safeguarded in accordance with legal requirements, for this reason it shall not be passed on to third parties, unless such disclosure is deemed suitable for your participation in our business and in the business carried out in collaboration with any of our business partners. This shall include the processing of your requests in relation to your use of our Brand/Website and/or the Games/Products or our business associates or unless the law expressly requires it. Relevant authorities, regulators, employees of the Company, more specifically those forming part of Customer Support Team and the Payments & Anti-Fraud teams as well as other selected employees, shall also have access to your Personal Information for the purpose of executing their duties and providing you with assistance. You hereby consent to such disclosures. 

### SELLING AND RELEASING OF DATA

    1. We do not sell personal data about our customers to third parties. However, we may release personal data if we acquire any new businesses. Should the Company undergo any changes to its structure such as a merger, acquisition by another company or a partial acquisition, it is most likely that our customers’ personal data will be included within the sale or transfer. We will, as part of our policy, inform our customers by email prior to affecting such transfer of personal data. 

We further reserve the right to release personal data when we believe that release is appropriate in order to comply with the law, or to enforce our Terms and Conditions, or to protect our rights, property, or safety, and also for the protection of any other companies within our group of companies. 

### LAWS AND REGULATIONS

    1. We hereby acknowledge that in collecting and processing your Personal Information for the purposes of managing your Member Account, we are bound by strict legal provisions on the protection of personal data. Consequently, we endeavour to protect your personal information and respect your privacy in accordance with best business practices and applicable regulations. In addition and for the avoidance of doubt, nothing in this Privacy Policy shall prevent us from retaining your Personal Information where we are required to do so by law. 

### RETENTION OF PERSONAL DATA

    1. As stated under our Terms and Conditions both, you and the Casino can decide to have your Member Account closed at any time. Following closure of your account, we will retain your personal data on record for as long as required by law. This data shall only be used should it be required by competent authorities in cases of enquiries regarding financial and fiscal records, fraud, money laundering or investigations into any other illegal activity. 

### CONTACTING US

    1. You may always contact us should you wish to:

a) Confirm the accuracy of the personal information we have collected about you;

b) Enquire about our use of your personal information;

c) Prohibit future use of your data for marketing purposes;

d) Update any information that you have provided us with, provided that in such cases you shall provide any evidence we may reasonably require to effect such changes. It is illegal to provide us with false information about you and it is your responsibility to ensure that we are always updated with your correct data. 

### COOKIE POLICY

    1. By accepting our Terms and Conditions, registering a Member Account and using our services, you acknowledge that the Website will use cookies in order to store some information on your computer, laptop, tablet or mobile device when you access our Website. 

Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer or equipment when you visit certain web pages. They record your preferences and send information from your browser, in order to help improve your Website experience and deliver a better and more personalised service. Furthermore, some of the cookies we use are essential for the Website to operate. 

If you wish to delete any cookies already stored on your computer or stop the cookies that keep track of your browsing patterns on this Website, you can do so by deleting your existing cookies and managing your browser's privacy settings to block them (Cookies can usually be changed on the “Settings” section of your browser). We recommend that you do not block or delete your cookies as this may restrict your use of our Website. 

### SECURITY OF PERSONAL DATA

    1. We are committed to providing secure services to players, and we will take all reasonable precautions to ensure that all the data that you have submitted via the Website remains safe. 

We use 128-bit SSL (Secure Socket Layer), the technology employed by many legal and financial institutions to guarantee the safety of all transactions performed on the Website. We only work with reputable and trusted payment processing providers to make sure that players’ deposits and withdrawals are handled carefully and according to industry standards. 

Player accounts can only be accessed with the player’s unique ID and password. The player is responsible for keeping their login information confidential and making sure it cannot be accessed by another person. 

### NETENT GAMES

    1. When you play casino games developed by NetEnt, NetEnt’s Privacy Policy also applies. This policy can be found [here](https://www.netent.com/en/netent-privacy-policy-eu/).
